温彻斯特太太
Mrs. Winchester,
我认为你就喜欢危险
I believe you're drawn to danger.
去喝一杯
Drink?
(忆往昔)
你最近跟妈妈通过话吗
Have you talked to Mom lately?
别担心你们妈妈
Oh, shouldn't worry about your Mum.
她和凯奇是很棒的组合
Her and Ketch make quite a team.
你会希望你妈跟他合作吗
Would you want your mom working with him?
真是没料到
Well, that was unexpected.
海斯博士  我不知道你离开了伦敦
Dr. Hess. I didn't think you left London.
我受命于其他长老
I have been tasked by the other elders
来挽救这急转直下的局面
to fix this rapidly deteriorating situation.
海斯博士
Dr. Hess --
这些猎人已经失控了
These hunters are out of control.
铲除他们
Exterminate them.
尤其是温家兄弟
The brothers Winchester, in particular.
(如今)
(威斯康辛州  托马霍克)
嗯  我还是走了
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go.
-什么  -明天还有工作呢
- What? - I got work tomorrow, so...
别  哥们  留下  再喝点啤酒
Naw, dude. Stick around. Have another beer.
好好看戏
Enjoy the show.
你知道你是个变态吧
You know you're a freak, right?
当然
Oh, yeah.
回见  哥们
Cheers, bud.
天呐  哥们
Ohh, man. Dude.
达利恩  这搞什么  哥们
Daryn! What is this, man?
太好笑了  达利恩
Hey, real funny, Daryn!
达利恩
Daryn?
不  不
No. No.
不不不
No, no, no!
[邪恶力量 第12季第18集]
这是我的语音信箱
This is my voicemail.
-请留你的语音邮件  -拜托
- Make your voice a mail. - Come on.
小卡  是我
Cass, it's me.
我尝试联系你好几天了
I've been trying to get ahold of you for days.
我不知道是怎么回事
I don't know what's going on,
但我们查到了大衮的线索
but we got a line on Dagon...
然后又被收拾了个惨
and we got our asses handed to us,
虽然有柯尔特枪
even with the Colt.
真的很需要支援
So...could really use the backup.
回电话
Call me back.
小卡还联系不上
So no luck with Cass, huh?
是啊  还是不知所踪
Yeah, still AWOL.
好吧  那我们找找他
All right, so let's find him.
我一直在找  萨姆
I've been trying, Sam.
他手机的定位系统关了
The GPS on his phone is turned off,
系统上也看不到
and there's nothing in the system about
奇怪风衣男被捕
some weird guy in a trench coat getting arrested
或死亡的消息
or turning up dead.
嗯
Right.
迪恩  这是小卡
Dean, it's Cass.
这也不是他第一次
I mean, this isn't the first time
消失不见了
he's dropped off the map, you know?
不管是怎么回事  他不会有事的
And whatever's happening, he'll be fine.
他一向没事
He always is.
是啊
Yeah.
你呢
What 'bout you?
你查到什么了吗  阅读彩虹
You got anything there, Reading Rainbow?
我整宿没睡
I stayed up all night,
翻查我们所有恶魔的资料
going through every book we have on demons,
原来  我们有很多关于恶魔的书
and it turns out we have a lot of books on demons.
有大衮的资料吗
Anything on Dagon?
偶尔有提到  但没什么可用的
Mentions here and there, but nothing we can use.
我猜  地狱王子
I guess the, uh, Princes of Hell
都很会低调做人
are pretty good at staying off the radar.
是啊  他们不就这样吗
Well, yeah, isn't that kind of their thing?
刚收到一封米克的电邮
Just got an e-mail from Mick.
有案子
It's a case.
-很好  -看来有个叫杰拉德·海耶斯的人
- Good.  - Looks like a guy named Jarrod Hayes
一周前在威斯康辛州的托马霍克失踪了
disappeared in Tomahawk, Wisconsin, a week ago.
无目击者  没有尸体
No witnesses. No body.
-但米克说这里有过类似案例  -什么意思
- But Mick says this place has a history. - Meaning?
就是说托马霍克常有人失踪
Well, it means a lot of people go missing in Tomahawk,
从1898到1997年  每年一个
one a year, every year, from 1898 to 1997,
然后再无失踪  直到现在
and then nothing until now.
隔了20年
So 20 years?
嗯  或许又开始了
Yeah. So maybe they're starting up again?
或许是某种循环
Maybe it's a cycle of some sort?
嗯
Well...
查查便知
one way to find out.
(萨姆  这就去)
准备行动
It's time.
(威斯康辛州  托马霍克)
抱歉  但联调局为什么对杰拉德·海耶斯感兴趣
I'm sorry, but why the Feds interested in Jarrod Hayes?
只是听命行事
Just followin' orders.
嗯
Yeah, um...
能跟我们讲讲案子吗
So what can you tell us about the case?
没什么好讲的
Well...nothing much to tell.
杰拉德和朋友去天顶山玩
Jarrod and his friends were hanging out at Weather Top.
是孩子们去林子里亲热的地方
This make-out spot the kids use out at the woods.
然后他丢下朋友想回家
And then he ditched his pals to hoof it home.
结果没到家
Never made it.
那么是有人绑走了他
So somebody snagged him?
-或许吧  -或许
- Maybe. - Maybe?
或许杰拉德的确是被绑了
Look, maybe Jarrod did get got.
我们在追查所有线索
We're working every lead.
但  要我说  他就是跑了
But you ask me, he just bailed.
-他为什么要那么做  -杰拉德挺艰辛的
- And why would he do that? - Jarrod's had it rough.
妈妈多年前就跑了  爸爸
Mom left years ago. And his dad...
这么说吧  杰拉德"经常摔下楼梯"
Well, let's just say Jarrod "fell down the stairs a lot,"
-懂吗  -等等
- you know what I mean. - Wait a second.
你既然知道他遭到了虐待  为什么不
If you knew he was being abused, why didn't you --
我们试过  试试从父母手里夺走孩子
We tried. Trying to take a child from his parents,
哪怕他们是世上最糟的人  也不容易
even if they're the worst people in the world, not easy.
你找过他爸吗
Did you talk to his old man?
没法找他谈
Can't. Not really.
他几年前中风了
Guy stroked out a couple years ago.
现在插管呼吸
Breathes through a tube.
猜猜谁还得照顾他
Guess who gets to take care of him?
你能想象要喂一个多年来
Can you imagine having to spoon-feed the guy
对你拳脚相加的人吃饭吗
that wailed on you for all those years?
人人都是有爆发点的
Everybody's got a breaking point.
如果杰拉德真跑了  我也不怪他
If Jarrod did blow town, I wouldn't blame him.
你说杰拉德失踪那晚是跟朋友在一起
You said that he was with friends the night Jarrod went missing.
嗯  他们有谁说什么了吗
Yeah, did any of them say anything?
没什么值得提的
Nothing worth repeatin'.
他多可爱
Ain't he precious?
知道我们去哪能找到这些朋友吗
Any idea where we can find these friends?
嗯  当然
Oh, yeah. Sure.
达利恩·波斯顿
Daryn Boston?
史塔克和马泰尔探员  联调局的
Agents Stark and Martell, FBI.
我去
Hell.
没事  不要紧
Yeah, no, it's cool.
医用  是吧
Medicinal purposes, right?
是吧
Yes?
是啊
Yeah.
我们只想谈谈
We just, uh, wanted to talk about
杰拉德·海耶斯失踪的那晚
the night Jarrod Hayes went missing.
怎么了
What about it?
治安官说你当时也在
Well, the Sheriff says you were with him.
治安官就是个混蛋
Yeah, well, the Sheriff is a jackass, all right?
他觉得杰拉德跑了
Look, he thinks Jarrod just skipped town.
-你不觉得吗  -我知道他没有
- You don't? - I know he didn't.
你跟警察说了吗
Did you tell that to the cops?
贝谢普治安官才不会信我呢
Man, Sheriff Bishop's not gonna believe me.
我们有...梁子
We got...history.
梁子
History?
每次镇上出事
Any time something happens in this town,
他都会叫我去问话
he brings me in for questioning.
为什么
Why is that?
-你觉得呢  -懂了
- Why do you think? - Right.
听着  如果你不肯把看到的事告诉治安官
Well, look, if you won't tell the Sheriff what you saw,
不如告诉我们吧
how 'bout you tell us?
救命  达利恩
Help! Daryn!
我跑去救杰拉德
Look, I ran to save Jarrod, okay?
-但是  -不不
- But... - No, no, no!
那怪物  抓走了他
The monster, it got him.
怪物
Monster?
黑比尔
Black Bill.
"黑比尔"是个本地传说
"Black Bill" is a local urban legend,
-能追溯到一百年前  -要续杯吗
- dates back more than a hundred years. - Warm it up?
-谢谢  -1907年的民间传说中
- Thank you. - A folklore story from 1907
提到了...
that -- that mentions that...
当时他被称为"黑威廉"
Uh, back then, he was called "Black William."
所以看来这期间
So it looks like some time between then and...
哥们  专心
Dude, focus.
我很专心的  嗯  黑比尔  查到啥了
I am focused. Yeah, Black Bill. What do you got?
好吧  他住在林子里
All right, well, he lives in the woods,
就像本地的泽西魔鬼
so he's like a local Jersey Devil.
据说  他长了山羊头
And apparently, he has the head of a goat.
山羊
A goat?
咩咩吗
Like... Goat?
对  山羊
Yeah, a goat.
或许达利恩看到的就是那个
Well, maybe that's what Daryn saw.
-除非你觉得他撒了谎  -就来
- Unless you think he was lying. - Yeah. Be right back.
我觉得他吓得不轻  不会是撒谎
I think he's a little too freaked out to be lying.
我们有个起了海盗名字的山羊男
So we got a, uh, goat dude with a name like a pirate,
这对于我们来说也够疯狂了
which is a little insane, even for us.
我们的标准可是超高的
And that bar is... super high.
如果是真的  它是什么
So if it is real, what the hell is it?
不知道
I'm not sure.
有好多人兽杂交的传说
I mean, there's tons of human-animal hybrid lore
能追溯到古埃及
dating back all the way to ancient Egypt.
嗯  你去查明到底是什么
Right, well, why don't you figure out what the hell it is,
我去想办法杀它  好吗
and I'll figure out a way to kill it. Okay?
好吧
All right.
好  别等我了
Right. Don't wait up.
-什么  -我已经有办法杀它了
- What? - I already figured out a way to kill it.
你怎么...你都不知道它是什么
How did you -- You don't even know what it is.
柯尔特  见神杀神
The Colt. Dusts anything.
要动脑  萨姆  别光傻用功
Work smarter, Sammy, not harder.
别来热咖啡那招
Oh, don't do the hot coffee thing.
这咖啡可真烫
Boy, this coffee is hot.
就像
Kind of like...
-你叫什么  -卡门
- What's your name? - Carmen.
对不起
Sorry.
该死  皮特
Damn it, Pete!
达利恩
Daryn...
我不想当坏人  但是
I don't wanna be the bad guy here, but...
你来迟了
you clocked in late.
-又一次  -那又如何
- Again. - Yeah, and?
你真的让我很没办法  哥们
And you're really painting me in a corner here, pal.
我知道你和杰拉德关系很好
Look, I know -- I know that you and Jarrod, you were close.
我也喜欢他的
And I liked him, too.
他是个好员工
He was a-a valued employee
是个好朋友
and he was a friend.
-是吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
因为你让他干兼职后
'Cause after you put him on part-time,
他恨死你了
he pretty much hated you.
我觉得他有那个权利
Well, I would say that that was his prerogative.
但你不能继续以他为理由消极怠工
But you can't keep using him as an excuse to blow off work.
-好吗  -嗯
- Okay? - Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
达利恩
Daryn, Daryn.
好有件事
One more thing.
你得少抽点大麻了
You gotta lay off the reefer.
好吗
All right?
至少明天别抽
At least for tomorrow.
明天很重要
It's a big day.
嗯  不不  我理解
Yeah. No, no, no. I understand.
嗯  好  得挂了
Yeah. Well... Yeah, gotta go.
回头见  好了
I'll see you later. Okay.
-昨晚挺爽  -棒呆了
- Good night? - Awesome.
昨晚棒呆了  太棒了
It was an awesome night. So awesome.
你还吃吗
You gonna eat that?
看来不吃了  请便吧
Guess not. Be my guest.
点一次薄煎饼能死啊
I mean, would it kill you to order pancakes? Once?
-好吧  你  -不不
- Okay, fine. You - No, no. No.
我忍忍吧
I'll deal.
你昨晚怎么样
How was your night?
很忙  另一种忙  不过很好
Busy. A different kind of a busy, but good.
嗯  读书  山羊仔查到什么了
Right. Books. Anything on goat dude?
嗯  查到一点
Yeah, little bit.
我大概知道我们面对的是什么了
I have some idea what we're dealing with.
看啊
Look at this.
是萨梯
It's a satyr --
希腊神话中半人半羊的神
half man, half goat from Greek mythology.
拜托  这家伙多可爱
Oh, come on. This guy's adorable.
还演奏长笛呢
He plays a freakin' flute.
是啊  迪恩  那是潘神  是他的长笛
Yeah, Dean. That's -- that's Pan. It's his flute.
听好  萨梯有无法控制的情欲
So listen, satyrs are creatures of uncontrollable lust.
他们会引人们去林子里群交
They would lead people to the woods for massive orgies.
真棒
Nice.
等玩乐结束  萨梯就
And when the fun was over, the satyr would,
"饱食受害者的肉体
"feast upon the flesh of his victims
直到被他们潮湿滑腻的肉涨了肚子"
until his belly was full to bursting with their moist, slippery meat."
好生动
That's descriptive.
好吧  我们怎么办
All right, what do we do?
我本想着  我们去找达利恩谈谈
Well, I was thinking that maybe we could go talk to Daryn,
看他看到的是不是这个
see if this is, indeed, what he saw.
-但是  -但他妈妈说
- But? - But his mom told me
达利恩昨晚下班后没回到家
Daryn never made it home from work last night.
别出差错
No screwups, right?
打扰  先生
Excuse me, sir.
史塔克和马泰尔探员  联调局
Agents Stark and Martell, FBI.
我们找达利恩·波斯顿
We're looking for Daryn Boston.
达利恩  他有麻烦了吗
Daryn? Is he in trouble?
不不  没有  我们昨天找过他
No, no, no, not at all. We -- we spoke with him yesterday.
只想问几个跟进问题
Just wanna ask a few follow-up questions.
他不在吗
I don't suppose he's around.
不  达利恩今天没来上班
No, Daryn -- Daryn didn't show up for work today.
那你最后见他是什么时候
So when was the last time you saw him?
昨晚  关门的时候
Last night. Closed up.
还谈了今天的大日子
Talked about our big day today.
什么大日子
What big day?
看到那边拿笔记板的了吗
You see that walking clipboard over there?
-嗯  -那是卫生检查员
- Yeah. - That's a health inspector.
他想让我们关门
He's trying to shut us down.
为什么  这里一尘不染
How come? This place is spotless.
是收拾得挺干净  但我们的设备
It cleans up pretty nice, but our equipment,
都有点过时了
it's a little out of date.
-不能升级吗  -能就升了
- Can't you upgrade? - We would if we could.
生意没那么兴隆
Business isn't exactly booming.
我们三个月前不得不关了半个厂子
We had to shut down half the plant three months back.
同时  我们的厂主宁可扮演治安官
Meanwhile, our owner would rather play sheriff
-而不是真正地打理生意  -等等
- than actually take care of business. - Wait a second.
你是说这厂子是贝谢普治安官的
You're telling me that Sheriff Bishop owns this place?
对  小巴里特·贝谢普
Yeah. Barrett Bishop, Jr.
贝谢普肉类帝国的继承人
Heir to the Bishop meat empire.
他的家族  一直是厂子的东家
His family, they've owned this plant for...forever.
巴里在里面  想哄好检查员
Barry's inside. He's hopin' to sweet talk the inspector.
要我说  没啥用  又太太迟了
You ask me, it's too little, way too late.
加芬克先生
Mr. Garfinkle.
失陪了
Excuse me.
嗯
Sure.
我们来到了镇上  查一桩案子
So we roll into town, look into a case,
找过了当地警方
talk to the local badge...
然后我们唯一的目击者就不见了
And then our one witness goes missing.
而他最后出现的地方是治安官的厂子
Last place he was seen owned by the Sheriff.
是巧合吗
Sound like a coincidence?
你饿了吗  我饿了
You hungry? I'm hungry.
打扰  治安官
Excuse me, Sheriff.
探员们  你们怎么来了
Agents. What are you guys doin' here?
我们也可以问你呢
Well, we could ask you the same thing,
不过  对了  这里是你的
except... Oh, right. You run the joint.
文件上是我的名字
Well, my name's on the paperwork.
但皮特负责日常管理
Pete handles the day to day.
你们还在找杰拉德·海耶斯吗
Are you still trying to chase down Jarrod Hayes?
是啊  还有达利恩·波斯顿
Yeah, and, uh, now Daryn Boston.
嗯  他似乎也失踪了
Yeah. Seems to have gone missing, too.
天呐  我才知道
Jeez. First I've heard of it.
嗯
Yeah.
告诉我们  你听说过黑比尔吗
So tell us, what have you heard about Black Bill?
-什么  -黑比尔
- I'm sorry. - Black Bill.
达利恩说他看到黑比尔袭击了杰拉德·海耶斯
Daryn told us he saw Black Bill attack Jarrod Hayes.
他不想告诉你  因为他觉得你不会相信
He didn't wanna tell ya 'cause he didn't think you'd believe him.
嗯  他说得对
Well -- well... Yeah. He's right.
在这里  父母会告诉孩子
Look, 'round here, parents tell their kids
别去林子里  否则会被黑比尔抓走
no to go into the woods or Black Bill will get 'em.
他就是黄毛妖怪
He's the bogeyman.
大家都知道妖怪不是真的
Everyone knows that the bogeyman ain't real.
你确定吗
Sure about that?
这镇上好像老有人失踪啊
Seems like a lot of people go missing in this town.
嗯  直到97年还是一年一个
Yeah, one a year every year up until '97.
是啊  好吧
Yeah. Okay.
人们会来到镇上
I mean, people come to town,
在工厂打一阵工
they work in the plant for a while,
然后他们无聊  待不住了
then they get bored and restless,
他们就会离开
and they, you know, move on.
达利恩呢
And Daryn?
或许达利恩是以为自己看见了黑比尔
You know, maybe Daryn thinks he say Black Bill,
但老实说
but let's be honest.
他要么是喝醉了  要么是嗑嗨了  要么都有
Kid was drunk, high, or both.
我敢打赌
And I'll bet you dollars to doughnuts,
达利恩只是在哪里把药劲睡过去呢
Daryn's just holed up, sleeping one off.
该死  他这会儿大概正安然无恙地醒来
Hell, he's probably waking up right now, safe and sound.
(危险  冷却剂泄露  勿入)
救命啊
Help, please!
救命
Help!
救救我
Help me!
治安官真是一点不可疑
Well, Sheriff's not acting suspicious at all.
-是啊  -但他跟山羊仔什么关系
- Right. - Yeah, but how is he connected to goat dude?
这是个好问题
Now that's a good question.
救命
Help!
救命啊
Help! Help! Please!
救救我
Help me! Help! Help! Help!
救命
Help!
不是吧  迪恩
Seriously? Dean?
我们刚刚看到那场景  你怎么吃得下肉
After what we just saw, how -- how can you eat?
成熟点吧  萨姆
Grow up, Sam, okay?
汉堡是牛肉  培根是猪肉  绿色食品是人肉
Burger's beef, bacon's pig, Soylent Green's people.
但这...
But this -- this...
这是天堂
This is heaven.
好吧  怎么样
Right. Um, so, uh, what's the word?
你有发现吗
You find anything?
算是吧
Yeah, kind of.
我交叉核对了所有失踪人员
So I cross-checked all the names of the people who went missing
和比尔钩肉厂的员工名单
with the employee roster at Billhook Meats.
怎样  还有其他受害人是厂里员工吗
And? Any more of the vics work at the plant?
都是
Try all of 'em.
都是  不是吧
All of 'em? Seriously?
那么  可以说
So I guess that means, safe to say that, uh,
黑比尔绝对跟肉厂有关
Black Bill is definitely connected to the plant?
嗯  或是跟厂主家族有关
Yeah. Or the family that runs it.
或是都有
Or both.
或许他们是另外还经营了邪恶宠物动物园
Well, maybe they just run an evil petting zoo on the side.
我去记录大厅查了查
So I, uh, spent some time at the Hall of Records.
贝谢普家族创建了托马霍克镇
The Bishops founded Tomahawk.
这里的一切  这是座公司小镇
Everything. This is a company town.
如果你住这儿  一定是厂子员工
If you lived here, you worked at the plant.
贝谢普家族拥有所有房产  所有小企业
The Bishops owned all the houses, all the businesses.
至少直到几年前  还是的
Or they did until a few years ago.
看来治安官一直在出售
Looks like the Sheriff has been selling off
他们的家族资产
all of their family property.
什么都卖
Uh, everything, really...
除了肉厂
except for the plant
和家族庄园
and the family estate.
那么亚当斯一家的大宅现在住着谁
So who lives at the Addams Family house?
(问问情况)
-是米克  -好吧
- It's Mick. - Okay.
告诉他我们一切都好
Tell him we're cool.
那么去恐怖大宅
So creepy house?
去恐怖大宅
Creepy house.
(没事  在查案)
没人  行动
It's clear. Onward.
记住你们的命令
Now remember your orders.
我们离开时
By the time we leave,
海斯博士想了解一切
Dr. Hess wants to know everything
我们的"朋友"温家兄弟的事
about our "friends" the Winchesters --
他们的同盟  他们的习惯
their allies, their habits.
萨姆的头发怎么会那么油亮
How does Sam get his hair so shiny?
迪恩有多少件破烂法兰绒
How many ratty flannels does Dean own?
快速工作  少说话  别留下痕迹
So work quick, work quiet, and leave no trace.
看来  米克让萨姆和迪恩
And apparently, Mick let Sam and Dean
拿走了柯尔特枪
get their hands on the bloody Colt.
找到它
Find it, huh?
看上去没人
Looks empty.
进去看看吧  或许能发现什么
Well, why don't we check inside? Maybe we'll get lucky.
迪恩
Dean.
有发现了
I'd say we just got lucky.
有人吗
Hello?
山羊仔
Goat dude?
为什么有钱人总是有问题
Why is it always the rich ones?
他们难道是  "门球挺好玩
I mean, what, are they, like, "Croquet's all right.
但知道什么更好吗
But you know what'd be great?
杀人"
Murder."
你好  治安官
Hiya, Sheriff.
说
Talk.
-并不是看上去那样的  -是吗
- This is not what it looks like. - Really?
因为我看像个杀人房
'Cause it looks like a straight up murder room to me.
治安官  怎么回事
Sheriff, what's goin' on?
你们不会相信的
You... you won't believe me.
说说看
Try us.
我们思想很开放的
We're pretty open mind.
我的家族
My family, we...
我们有个秘密
got a secret.
好家庭都有
All the best ones do.
这是关于黑比尔吗
Is this about Black Bill?
不  也是  但他不是真的
No. I mean, yeah, but...he's not real.
黑比尔  是我们
Black Bill, he's...us.
什么
Come again?
小时候  我爸跟我讲过一个怪物
Growing up, my father'd tell me stories about a monster.
住在我们家下面  保佑我们发财
Lived under our house and made our family rich.
我们只需要  给它食物
All we had to do was -- was feed it.
-给它什么  -血
- Feed it what? - Blood.
人血
Human blood.
我爸爸  他爸爸  他们的祖先
My dad, his dad, and all the way back,
他们会出去  随便抓个可怜人
they'd go out and grab some poor son of a bitch,
带来这里
bring 'em here and...
他们动手时  会戴个面具
When they did it they wore a mask.
黑比尔
Black Bill...
是我们编造的
We made him up.
那么山羊仔就是个人
So goat dude is just a dude?
那怪物是谁
Then who's the monster?
摩洛神
Moloch.
祭祀神
God of sacrifice.
抱歉  你们家地下室住了个神
What, I'm sorry. You -- you have a god living in your basement?
是啊  我的一个祖先  束缚住了摩洛神
Yeah, one of my people way back, they bound Moloch,
把他关了起来
locked him away...
让他挨饿
starved him.
我的家族  我们就是这么干的
My family, that's what we did.
我们让神饿得不行
We let the god get so hungry that
愿为喝血不惜一切
he'd do anything for blood.
摩洛神用它的法力让我们发财
Moloch used his power to make us rich.
我父亲97年死后  我中止了那一切
After my father died in '97, I put a stop to all of that.
我做不到
Look, I couldn't...
我没杀过人  我只想帮助他人
I never killed anybody. I just wanted to help people
弥补我们做过的一切恶事
to make up for all the bad we've done.
我想
I wanted...
留下一份遗产
to leave a legacy.
你可真好
Well, aren't you just a peach?
那么摩洛神呢
So what happened to Moloch?
我关着他
I kept him locked up.
本希望他能饿死
Hoped he'd starve to death.
关在哪了
Locked up where?
-是空的  -什么
- It's empty. - What?
-是空的  -不不不
- It's empty. - No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
待在这儿  盯住他
Stay here. Keep an eye on him.
什么  迪恩  楼上可能是个神
What? Dean, there could be a god up there.
我没问题的
I'm cool.
迪恩
Dean?
开门
Open up!
给
Here. Here.
-你干什么呢  -我在追踪迪恩的手机
- What are you doing? - I'm trying to track Dean's cellphone.
好了  找到了  走吧
All right, got it. Let's go.
我就知道
Just as I thought.
什么都看不到
Can't see a damn thing.
皮特  这地方不错
Hiya, Pete. Nice digs.
没想到会再见到你  探员
I didn't expect to see you again, Agent.
我是去宅子里找我哥哥的
I went to the house looking for my brother.
-哥哥  -巴里
- Brother? - Barry.
异母  同父
Different moms, same daddy.
贝谢普老爹啊
Old man Bishop, he, uh,
他喜欢女人
he had an eye for the ladies.
镇上的人都知道  但又能如何
Everyone in town knew about it, but didn't make a difference.
巴里在大宅子里长大  而我在流动房屋里长大
Barry grew up in the big house. I grew up in a double wide.
你觉得公平吗
Does that sound fair to you?
老实说  听上去像一集不怎么样的《豪门恩怨》
Honestly? Sounds like a bad episode of "Dynasty"
你挺会说笑
You got a lot of jokes.
现在  我也没别的了
Yeah, right now, that's about all I got.
是啊
Right.
知道我有什么吗
You know what I got?
一个神
A god.
摩洛神
Moloch.
对了
Bingo!
巴里那样到处散财
With Barry giving away the family fortune like that,
我只能发挥创意
I had to get creative.
我去老宅
I went to the old house,
想拿点能卖的东西
trying to get my hands on anything I could sell.
但我却找到了别的
But I found somethin' else.
摩洛神
Moloch.
他说他能让我发财
He told me he'd make me rich.
他说能解决我所有问题
He told me he'd solve all my problems.
我只需要给他血
All I had to do was feed him.
而且  我是个贝谢普家人
And hell, I'm a Bishop.
我们就做这个  是吧
That's what we do, right?
猎人  杀人
Hunting people. Killing them.
家族事业
The family business.
摩洛神已经饿了20年了
Moloch's been starved for 20 years.
他要吃几顿才能恢复法力
It's gonna take a few meals for him to get his mojo goin',
但等到时  我们就东山再起了
but then... Oh, we are back, baby.
是啊  我要挽救这小镇
Yeah. I'm savin' this town.
跟杰拉德和达利恩说去
Well, I'll tell that to Jarrod and Daryn.
杰拉德是个废物  他活该
Jarrod was a screwup. He got what he deserved.
达利恩  抱歉  伙计  但他既然开口了
And Daryn? Well, sorry, bud, but once he talked,
就必须死
he had to go.
这叫善后
Loose ends, you know?
善后  拜托
Loose ends. Come on!
我的混蛋异母哥哥本该做下一顿餐的
My jackass half-brother was supposed to be the next meal,
但你也凑合
but you'll do.
皮特  我们谈谈嘛
W-- Pete, let's just talk about this.
听着  我们...
Listen... Let's --
很快就结束了
It'll be over soon.
多谢帮忙
Thanks for helpin' out!
什么
What...
搜查已完成  长官
The sweep's complete, sir.
我们已经拍照  收录了一切
We've photographed and catalogued every inch.
-柯尔特呢  -没有
- And the Colt? - I'm afraid not.
肯定是被温家兄弟带走了
The Winchesters must have it.
该死
Bugger.
-走吗  -嗯
- Shall we go? - Yes.
还有一件事
Just one last thing.
好了  我想喝一杯
Now then, I could use a pint.
皮特
Pete!
迪恩
Dean?
(危险)
迪恩
Dean?
出来啊  你个混蛋
Come on, you son of a bitch.
皮特
Pete!
你得停手
You have to stop.
别装作你在乎
Don't act like you care.
我把厂子给了你
I gave you the plant.
因为你知道厂子不行了
Because you knew it was failing.
真是屁话
What a bunch of crap.
这就是我得到的东西
That's what I get.
我这辈子得到的都是破烂
I get that my whole life! The crap!
今后不会了  我要救小镇
Not anymore. I'm saving this town.
我是英雄
I'm the hero.
你死定了
And you're dead.
柯尔特
Colt.
见神杀神
Dusts anything.
感觉怎么样
How you feelin'?
好像刚跟个神打了12回合
Like I just went 12 rounds with a god.
正常
So, you know...normal.
-嗯  -你们走吧
- Yeah. - You should go.
不  治安官  我们可以帮忙收拾
No, Sheriff, uh, we can help clean up.
不用
No.
我能解决
This...I'll take care of it.
我来吧
It's on me.
这个
This?
是我的遗产
This is my legacy.
嗯
Yep.
下次我再说我们家太乱套
Next time you hear me say that our family is messed up,
提醒我  我们至少不是疯子羊家族
remind me that we could be psycho goat people.
是啊  不假
Yeah, that's true enough.
我...
You know, I was...
想了贝谢普的话
thinking about what Bishop said.
关于
About...
你觉得我们会留下怎样的遗产
What do you think our legacy's gonna be?
等我们死了  我们做了那么多
When we're gone, I mean, after all the stuff we've done,
你觉得会有人记得我们吗
you think folks will remember us?
比如一百年后
You know, like, a hundred years from now?
不会
No.
太好了
That's nice.
我是说
Well, I mean...
我们这种人
guys like us, we're not exactly the type of people
是不会名留青史的
they write about in history books, you know?
但我们救的人
But the people we saved,
他们是我们的遗产
they're our legacy.
他们会记得我们  那么  我想
And they'll remember us and then I guess...
我们最终也会淡去
we'll eventually fade away, too.
那没关系
That's fine,
因为我们留下了一个更好的世界
because we left the world better than we found it, you know.
不知道这里会怎么样
I wonder what's gonna happen to this place.
等我们死了  会有猎人住进来
After we're gone, you think some hunter'll move in,
继续坚持猎魔吗
keep fightin' the fight?
希望吧
Yeah, I hope so.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
你干什么
What are you doin'?
留下印记
Leaving our mark.
给
Here.
我想我们该打给米克  汇报一下
Guess we gotta call Mick, debrief or whatever.
嗯
Right.
你们好  温彻斯特
Hello, Winchester.
凯奇
Ketch?
-米克呢  -他没说吗
- Where's Mick? - Oh, he didn't tell you?
他昨晚飞回了伦敦
He flew back to London last night.
因为
After all the...
大衮和兰尼的破事
oh, unpleasantness with Dagon and Renny, well...
米克要承担责任的
Mick has a lot to answer for.
所以  你们暂时要向我汇报
So for the time being, you'll report to me.
不是吧
Seriously?
我也并不喜欢这样
I don't like it any more than you do.
我更想跟你们妈妈在一起
I'd much rather be with your mother.
猎魔
Hunting.
在德州猎杀山羊吸血怪
For...chupacabra in Texas.
但现在  你们只有我了
But for now, I'm what you've got.
威斯康辛州
So...Wisconsin?
-我们打赢了一个神  -干得好
- We fought a god and won. - Well done.
我们再联系
We'll be in touch.
我们要向低配版的克里斯蒂安·贝尔汇报了
So now we're reporting to low rent Christian Bale?
不是吧
Seriously?
我不喜欢那家伙  他让我不舒服
I don't like that guy. He creeps me out.
嗯
Yeah.
而且他骑最老  最烂
And he rides the oldest, worst,
最不可靠的机车
most unreliable bike.